<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/xsl.xml"?>

<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

<title>Blog</title>
<link href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/" />
<subtitle>Rambles and rants by Coby Cat</subtitle>
<author><name>CobyCat</name></author>

<entry>
<title>You've Yeed Your Last Haw</title>
<link href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/youve-yeed-your-last-haw.html" />
<id>https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/youve-yeed-your-last-haw.html</id>
<content type="xhtml">
<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><p>Germany really loved westerns, as you may know. That's a bit outside of the scope of my website for now, though maybe I'll get to it someday. Still, Belgium also had a strong fondness for the genre, as you can see in my article about <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/misc-articles/western/villages.html">Cowboy villages</a>. You know, I actually got some research help from my friends over at the 32-bit Café. Even deeply personal websites like mine can be a team effort! 🤠</p>
<p>In other site news, I've got rid of some external frameworks I used to imitate GUIs in some obscure corners of my websites. This should make my site leaner in case you venture that deeply.</p>
<p>I've been listening to a bunch of DungeonSynth albums, way too many to all list them out. Gonna opt to highlight a recent compilation then: <cite><a href="https://dungeonsynthcompilation.bandcamp.com/album/c14-the-black-keep">C14: The Black Keep</a></cite>, which is conceptualized as a sort of oldschool D&amp;D adventure.</p>
<p><cite><a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1448780/Jewel_Match_Origins__Palais_Imperial_Collectors_Edition/">Jewel Match Origins: Palais Imperial</a></cite> is a game I've been enjoying lately. I like a good themed Match 3 game, but I especially like that the jewels are rendered in a realistic fashion. Many mobile Match 3 games I've played have the most gorgeous artwork, just to resort to clashing cartoony gems regardless.</p>
</div>
</content>
<updated>2025-05-03T00:00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Recruit a Team of Teenagers With Attitude!</title>
<link href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/recruit-a-team-of-teenagers-with-attitude.html" />
<id>https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/recruit-a-team-of-teenagers-with-attitude.html</id>
<content type="xhtml">
<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><p>Today I bring you two new articles, which are more on the personal recollections side of the spectrum. Both feature genuine (but edited) childhood pictures! First, my recollections of <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/misc-articles/rangers/index.html">Power Rangers</a>. And then the start of a subsection on <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/bricks/index.html">LEGO</a>. For now, it remains just a personal essay (with a nice new Coby face though!), but I do hope to enhance this with some shrines and subpages later on.</p>
<p>Beyond that, I’ve done some visual and structural clean-up—my About page has been redesigned, and the index page got a refresh. No drastic changes, just a little polish to keep things looking nice.</p>
<p>I've been spending a lot of time ripping disks and downloading obscurer tape recordings, growing my Plex server as a convenient complement to my extensive physical media collection. Organizing files and adding metadata is a great distraction from everything that's going on. At least one tiny part of the world that'll make sense.</p>
<p>I don't have a new indie music album for you, I'm afraid. I don't listen to enough new music to keep up a steady stream of recommendations! 😅 Maybe a specific song from a few years back, then? Scizzie's <cite><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DP3rDP02lE0">Aquatic Ambience</a></cite> is a remix of the eponymous <cite>Donkey Kong Country</cite> song. It's become associated with nostalgic content on shortform video websites, and I guess that's why it stuck with me.</p>
</div>
</content>
<updated>2025-03-27T00:00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>The Spark That Will Light The Fire</title>
<link href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/the-spark-that-will-light-the-fire.html" />
<id>https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/the-spark-that-will-light-the-fire.html</id>
<content type="xhtml">
<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><p>Hey folks! A considerable amount of weight has been lifted from my shoulders.</p>
<p>For now, I bring to you a small but impactful update: the first new navigation button to this site since its inception. It leads to a <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/portfolio/index.html">portfolio page</a>, linking to some of my artwork that is already on this website, but also to a substantial (yet abandoned) effort to create Pokémon-inspired creatures inspired by Belgian culture, and some silly image edits.</p>
<p>With that more directly creative aspect added to the existing line-up, I think my website is finally starting to offer a somewhat comprehensive overview of the Coby Cat persona. I'm phrasing it like that because not everything I, the real person behind this persona, do or care for necessarily fits within the scope of this site. Political takes which have been sitting in my drafts folder for many months while I contemplate the merits versus the potential downsides of its inclusion. And, yes, unpleasant personal baggage that will never sully this site at all.</p>
<p>Still, there is always more that could be added that's definitely within scope. I have not yet written in depth about the LEGO themes that captures my childhood imagination: Adventurers, Castle, Slizer, Bionicle. Nor have I written about Edutainment software and games, of which I have an extensive physical collection for PC and CD-i. I'm not even mentioning all the various media and snippets of internet culture I am fond of. And I've also been pondering <s>my orb</s> whether a sub-site in Dutch could cover bits of Belgian nostalgia that I don't think have much international value. Rest assured, this site will never ever truly be complete.</p>
<p>I've been listening again to <cite>Goldenrod Citypop</cite>: <em><a href="https://gamegrooves.bandcamp.com/album/goldenrod-citypop-gold-version">Gold</a></em> and <em><a href="https://gamegrooves.bandcamp.com/album/goldenrod-citypop-silver-version">Silver</a></em>. I don't dig every track, but I do dig enough of it. And as a whole, it's a great love letter to my favorite generation of Pokémon.</p>
</div>
</content>
<updated>2025-03-08T00:00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Butter Scraped Over Too Much Bread</title>
<link href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/butter-scraped-over-too-much-bread.html" />
<id>https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/butter-scraped-over-too-much-bread.html</id>
<content type="xhtml">
<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><p>Welcome again to my humble abode.</p>
<p>This month, I wrote about <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/misc-articles/americanstock/index.html">American Stockhouses in Belgium </a>, stores that originally sold American military surplus, as a follow-up to earlier articles describing the European fascination with the US. The current swift collapse of American liberal democracy may well be the final death blow to that admiration, but let's hope it won't come to that.</p>
<p>With personal tragedy piled on top of the geopolitical tragedies, maybe I am just getting numb to it all. I've been archiving rare uploads from YouTube and the Internet Archive on my Plex server. Organizing things and adding metadata… it's a great distraction from everything. At least one tiny part of the world that'll make sense.</p>
<p>Anyway, I've got a more direct sequel article as well. My earlier <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/food/belgium.html">article about Belgian food</a> now has <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/food/belgium_fusion.html">a follow-up dedicated to (fast) food in Belgium that's still perceived as foreign</a>, specifically focusing on the cuisines that are considered (but are not really authentically) Italian, Chinese and Turkish.</p>
<p><a href="https://deepgnome.bandcamp.com/album/wanderlore">Wanderlore</a>, an album by Dungeon Synth artist Deep Gnome, has been of some comfort. The opening quote sampled from the 1977 Hobbit movie sets the right cozy vibe immediately. Appropriately, a wizard Coby variant has appeared on <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/aboutpages/OCs.html">my OCs page</a>.</p>
</div>
</content>
<updated>2025-02-22T00:00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>With Thunderous Applause</title>
<link href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/with-thunderous-applause.html" />
<id>https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/with-thunderous-applause.html</id>
<content type="xhtml">
<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><p>What a year, huh! What, it's only January? 💀</p>
<p>What's your poison in these <em>interesting</em> times? Mine's, as always, nostalgia. So I've got a <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/aesthetics/design/sala.html">short new page about Pierre Sala's designs</a>, in particular his pencil-based furniture. And I've finally finished a page that I've been working on for over year now: my <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/nostalgia/tabletop.html">memories of tabletop gaming</a>, which you can find through my about page as well.</p>
<p>I'm not ashamed to admit that I kind of enjoy watching some short-form video content to kill some downtime. I like seeing people's dogs, thrift hauls, fun crafts, as well as the various artful explorations of liminality. Since Tiktok's bizarre automated systems banned my purely passive account, I turned to Instagram. But because of <em>recent events</em>, my experience has gotten a lot worse. The political filter has been kneecapped, and I can no longer view the chronological feed of reels from accounts I follow. What a bummer!</p>
<p>Since that experience has worsened, I've been dabbling with mobile games again. Specifally ones that I can safely turn off at short notice. <a href="https://tann.fun/games/dice/">Slice &amp; Dice</a> ticks all the boxes for me, and I've been playing it quite a bit lately.</p>
<p>An album, then, to fly you away from here. <a href="https://kavakon.bandcamp.com/album/tiki-for-the-atomic-age">Tiki for the Atomic Age</a>. Written as an escape from a crumbling city, hopefully, it can also help us escape from a world that seems to be crumbling.</p>
<p>To round things off, I've been cleaning up and polishing various bits and bobs of my website. The most noticeable change will be my new logo.</p>
</div>
</content>
<updated>2025-01-26T00:00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>When the Saint Nicks Go Marching In</title>
<link href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/when-the-saint-nicks-go-marching-in.html" />
<id>https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/when-the-saint-nicks-go-marching-in.html</id>
<content type="xhtml">
<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><p>The Americans haven't even celebrated Thanksgiving yet, and Coby's here already with a double dose of Santa Claus? Not to worry, there's a good reason for that, as you can read in my <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/misc-articles/holidays/sinterklaas.html">newest article about a holiday in Belgium</a></p>
<p>Staying in the spirit of not-quite-christmas, maybe <a href="https://vreemdeopties.bandcamp.com/album/space-age-santa-outer-space-christmas-kitsch">this compilation of old atypical spacey Christmas songs</a> can set the mood.</p>
<p>I've been playing quite a bit of <a href="https://www.playbalatro.com/">Balatro</a> lately. Sometimes it shocks me that things are often mainstream and hyped for good reason! 😲 It reminds me strongly of all the Yahtzee I played during my childhood, both physically and digitally, scratching that same itch. There's apparently already <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2797650/Pip_My_Dice/">a Yahtzee-based clone</a> being worked on, and I'll probably check out its demo once I get a bit bored with Balatro.</p>
</div>
</content>
<updated>2024-11-25T00:00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Spooky Times</title>
<link href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/spooky-times.html" />
<id>https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/spooky-times.html</id>
<content type="xhtml">
<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><p>I had taken a bit of a break from webweaving, but Coby's back! <em>(Alright!)</em></p>
<p>I'm squeezing in just in time to submit something to another <a href="https://32bit.cafe/halloween24/">32-Bit Cafe event</a>, with a page about <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/misc-articles/holidays/halloween.html">Halloween in Belgium</a>. I hope to eventually get to making such pages for all the major holidays.</p>
<p>Daniel White has dropped a new bit of <em>encartacore</em> music, titled <em><a href="https://dwhite914.bandcamp.com/track/studyscape">Studyscape</a></em>. In these trying days, the dreamy promise of a better future is a welcoming consolation.</p>
<p>Some small updates have happened here and there. I stumbled upon a new IMAX DVD release, which I've added to the <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/misc-articles/imax/index.html">IMAX page</a>.</p>
<p><em>Agatha All Along</em> has some of the funnest witchery I've seen on the screen in a long time. But it all feels… lessened when you think of it all existing in a multiverse of superheroes and whatnot. I really wish it could have been its own thing, rather than just another MCU vehicle. But as it stands, I'm still having a darn good time with it.</p>
</div>
</content>
<updated>2024-10-27T00:00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Thinking Big</title>
<link href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/thinking-big.html" />
<id>https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/thinking-big.html</id>
<content type="xhtml">
<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><p>This month's big article was written for <a href="https://32bit.cafe/~xandra/events/codejam5/">the 32-Bit Cafe's latest Code Jam</a> which is as of the time of writing still ongoing. Originally intended as a small section of my article on motion ride simulation videos, it quickly grew in scope and size to the behemoth I present to you today. What's it about? <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/misc-articles/imax/index.html">IMAX movies on home video</a>, with some asides about IMAX in general and an early 3D encoding for home use.</p>
<p>Have you heard of <a href="https://dreamcastletm.bandcamp.com/album/e-n-t-e-r-t-h-e-d-r-e-a-m-c-a-s-t-l-e">Dreamcastle</a> before? These Vaporwave and Plunderphonics tracks evoke 90s and early 2000s Lego and Sega, two topics that speak to me very much. I believe they first came to my attention because of the elaborate custom cassette packaging they sent out to Lego YouTuber <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3Kkd1rVSY7A">R.R. Slugger</a>. The <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wgXPGP2A3Rk">trailer for their new album</a> also has to be seen to be believed.</p>
<p>To accompany my big article of the month, I have started a page that tries to get an overview of the <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/misc-articles/nwave/index.html">entire nWave catalog</a>, a Belgian animation studio. With these two efforts behind me, I hopefully can start expanding the motion ride simulator page in the future.</p>
</div>
</content>
<updated>2024-08-17T00:00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Silicon Dreams</title>
<link href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/silicon-dreams.html" />
<id>https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/silicon-dreams.html</id>
<content type="xhtml">
<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><p>My article about the <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/games/fantasyonline/index.html">the defunct Chinese Disney MMO</a> got some juicy updates thanks to tips from a friend over on Discord. The installer is still around, and we can even extract 3D models! Best of all, I'm explaining how you can do it as well.</p>
<p>Last time, I highlighted a concept album by Lookfar. <a href="https://louiezong.bandcamp.com">Louie Zong</a>, the artist behind Lookfar, has a varied selection of other concept albums which I've been enjoying. Gonna give a shout-out to <a href="https://louiezong.bandcamp.com/album/funky-friends">Funky Friends</a>, which evokes the acid jazz of Hey Arnold. Good stuff!</p>
<p>I've whipped up a quick little page about <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/misc-articles/motion/index.html">motion simulator videos</a>, specifically the one I brought up earlier on my <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/misc-articles/centerparcs/index.html">Center Parcs</a> page. I want this to be a stepping stone towards a broad curated selection of similar ride videos, so feel free to send in your own recommendations and recollections! And if you know anything more about the videos already described, please also get in touch!</p>
<p>For <a href="https://tilde.32bit.cafe/~ribose/events/destination/map.html">yet another code jam over at the 32-Bit Café</a>, I wrote a page about my early days on the internet. Since the code jam has run its course, I've properly linked to my entry on my own site. Try finding it, or resort to the <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/aboutpages/journey/index.html">boring no-fun shortcut</a>.</p>
</div>
</content>
<updated>2024-07-12T00:00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Mansion</title>
<link href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/mansion.html" />
<id>https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/mansion.html</id>
<content type="xhtml">
<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><p>Our tour of Michael Jackson's Neverland Ranch finally continues <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/neverland/mansion.html">into the mansion</a>, aided by a 3D model I created. There's still a lot we need to cover, so if you're a die-hard fan who knows a lot about the mansion, please hit me up so we can collaborate towards an improved model and tour!</p>
<p>Music-wise, I'm quite digging <a href="https://louiezong.bandcamp.com/album/mineral-hall">Mineral Hall</a>, a concept album which kinda feels like it bridges Dungeon Synth and the musical evocation of the so-called Utopian Scholastic aesthetic that I enjoy (like the Daniel White album I mentioned in a previous post). The cover art has the right sort of aesthetic, and the instrumentation also hits just right. Good stuff!</p>
<p>I've collected some <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/games/fantasyonline/index.html">rare screenshots of a defunct Chinese Disney MMO</a>. The game always intrigued me, and I'm sad I never got to play it. There are many other defunct Disney games that I actually played that maybe merit a page as well, at some point.</p>
</div>
</content>
<updated>2024-05-20T00:00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Comics</title>
<link href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/comics.html" />
<id>https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/comics.html</id>
<content type="xhtml">
<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><p>Today I bring to you a page about <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/comics/belgium.html">Belgian comics</a>, written from the perspective of someone who grew up surrounded with heavy comic fans but never being terribly invested in them. This serves as part of a larger series of pages I'm writing, to present a sort of accessible pop-cultural canon of Belgium, so to speak, and one specifically for a non-Belgian audience.</p>
<p>No music recommendation from me this time, but I can recommend a free game that I've been enjoying lately. <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2373630/Moonring/">Moonring</a> is a homage to old role-playing games like the Ultima series, with a timeless neon aesthetic and a rather brooding vibe. Also comes with a nice dungeon synth soundtrack!</p>
<p>A short page I whipped up for <a href="https://tilde.32bit.cafe/~hermit/community_jam_3/submissions.html">a code jam over at the 32-Bit Café</a> has finally been made public on my website. You can find it linked on my about page, or take <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/aboutpages/butwhy.html">a sneaky shortcut</a>.</p>
</div>
</content>
<updated>2024-04-25T00:00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Holidays</title>
<link href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/holidays.html" />
<id>https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/holidays.html</id>
<content type="xhtml">
<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><p>I actually managed to finish a first iteration of the update I had hoped to get out last month, when I got hit by scope creep. The result is my page on <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/misc-articles/centerparcs/index.html">Center Parcs</a>. I do intend to expand this page eventually.</p>
<p>I bought the <a href="https://dwhite914.bandcamp.com/album/pangeapedia-plus">Pangeapedia Plus</a> album I recommended in my first blog post. I probably shouldn't have. Don't get me wrong, it's an amazing album and it was very swiftly and correctly shipped by the artist! But dang, international shipping has gotten way worse lately. I had to pay massive fees to Belgian customs… 😓</p>
<p>A small page I added is <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/aboutpages/OCs.html">one for my OCs</a>. It's small for now, but maybe I'll uncover some more from the depths of my memory soon.</p>
<p>Some music I'd like to highlight this time is the soundtrack of the Bionicle fangame Masks of Power. <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cKaQyp__dQw">Calm Sands of Motara (Po-Wahi Night)</a>, for example, really manages to capture (and even expand on) the feel of early Bionicle.</p>
</div>
</content>
<updated>2024-03-22T00:00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Site Redesign</title>
<link href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/site-redesign.html" />
<id>https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/site-redesign.html</id>
<content type="xhtml">
<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><p>This is not the update I was hoping to get out by now! I started on a page, and got struck by my eternal enemy: scope creep. I wanted to add some photos, so I dug out old family photo albums, and then I found photo negatives. Long story short, I scanned over a thousand photos. And when I finally got back to writing the page, I got hit by writer's block.</p>
<p>So have a complete site redesign instead! I've taken inspiration from <a href="https://www.theskinsfactory.com/uiux-design-blog/a-look-back-on-our-design-work-for-the-walt-disney-company">Skins Factory designs for the Disney company</a> around 2007, and other designs on the slightly more playful and colorful side of what is now called Frutiger Aero. There are some aspects on various pages that still date from the old design, in particular the backgrounds, but that's alright. I can deal with those later.</p>
<p>I recently started gratitude journaling using <a href="https://momentory.app/">Momentory</a>, but I'm not sure if I can keep this up daily. It's part of my effort to adopt a more optimistic outlook on life, as I touched on in an earlier blog post.</p>
<p>One new page I was able to add is one with <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/misc-articles/book-reviews.html">book reviews</a>. Only one of the book reviews is actually written out to a satisfying degree, but hey, it's a start!</p>
<p>A song I'd like to highlight in this blog post is <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q4XTm7mQctk">Love Maria</a> by Crazy Loop. Crazy Loop was a one album project by O-Zone founder Dan Balan (who you probably know from their hit <em>Dragostea Din Tei</em>, better known as <em>Numa Numa</em> or <em>Maya Hi</em>). His original album, the Power of Shower, was released in 2006. I discovered it several years later and instantly fell in love. Balan has since been active in Ukraine. In 2023 Crazy Loop returned, with a new music video filmed in and dedicated to the beautiful city of Kyiv.</p>
</div>
</content>
<updated>2024-02-25T00:00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Belgian Food</title>
<link href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/belgian-food.html" />
<id>https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/belgian-food.html</id>
<content type="xhtml">
<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><p>Well, this is a big one! I had this crazy ambitious idea, and despite feeling burnt out on it multiple times, I managed to pull it off! I wrote <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/food/belgium.html">an article all about Belgian fast food, candies, and more</a>, lovingly illustrated in a cohesive style to tie it all together! I really challenged myself — both on writing and illustrating — and this was probably too much for me… but I am really proud of what I accomplished. Just, um… please don't  expect this level of quality for future site updates! 😅</p>
<p>The past week I've been listening to Gold Casio again, a criminally underrated disco and synth-pop band. I highly recommend checking out <a href="https://goldcasio.bandcamp.com/track/last-song">Last Song</a>, which is one of their older songs, and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oXCB1X_IWHw">$$</a>, which is a newer one.</p>
<p>Oh, and I've spruced up some texts here and there, so they read and flow a bit more smoothly. No worries, the actual content is still the same!</p>
</div>
</content>
<updated>2024-01-26T00:00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>More housekeeping</title>
<link href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/more-housekeeping.html" />
<id>https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/more-housekeeping.html</id>
<content type="xhtml">
<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><p>A quick little update! I've added some more buttons to my <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/buttons/index.html">Button Wall</a>, expanded my <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/links.html">links</a> page yet again and added a new <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/video-links.html">video links</a> page.</p>
<p>A rather forgotten part of my website is the <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/tools/profilepimper">Spacehey Profile Pimper</a> I created for someone in the 32-Bit Café. There are no links to it from my website, since I never really found a good spot for it. Feel free to reach out with your ideas!</p>
<p>I had hoped to get a new article out in this update as well, but I didn't get one of my many works-in-progress up to my standards yet. Maybe some other time then. This is, after all, a hobby and not a job. 😀</p>
<p>A pretty obscure song I'd like to highlight is <a href="https://newcenturyboys.bandcamp.com/track/money-can-buy-happiness">Money Can Buy Happiness</a> by New Century. Maybe I should also find a proper spot on my website to bundle these music recommendations in my blog posts, haha.</p>
</div>
</content>
<updated>2024-01-12T00:00:00</updated>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>A New Beginning</title>
<link href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/a-new-beginning.html" />
<id>https://cobycat.neocities.org/blog/a-new-beginning.html</id>
<content type="xhtml">
<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><p>I've added a little blog to my site, as you'll have noticed (since you're reading this). You'll probably find notifications about site updates here, and some quick thoughts. Proper longform content I will probably reserve for regular pages, as I prefer their timeless nature. These pages are being generated automatically, a first for my site, but I'll spare you the dull details of all that techy nonsense.</p>
<p>I've been listening to <a href="https://dwhite914.bandcamp.com/album/pangeapedia-plus">Pangeapedia Plus</a> again lately. Probably should buy the album one of these days, but international shipping is such a pain in the wallet. To get this new year off to a good start I'm embracing the bright-eyed optimism of the so-called Utopian Scholastic aesthetic. Let's pick up where we left off, and make 👏 history 👏 end 👏 again 👏.</p>
<p>A rather obscure part of my website that's not really easy to find except by stumbling upon it is my <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/nostalgia/pc.html">Visual Memories of Computing</a> page. I probably made it too tedious to find. Some of the screenshots lead to subpages, others lead to relevant links. See if you can find the intended way of accessing this page! Eventually I'll be adding some other overviews like that. One about board games is in the works, for example.</p>
<p>One memory of computing not on that page is “Active Desktop”. Until the late days of Windows XP, you could set an HTML page as your desktop background. That was pretty fun, and I regularly made use of that back in the day.</p>
<p>For this first blog post I haven't really got any exciting updates to share. Based on some remarks by patrons of the <a href="https://32bit.cafe/">32-Bit Café</a> a while back, I've overhauled my <a href="https://cobycat.neocities.org/links.html">links</a> page to include some context on the links. Links pages are my favorite part of personal websites, especially now that major search are flooded with low-quality results, so I want to make my own links page as good as it can be.</p>
</div>
</content>
<updated>2024-01-05T00:00:00</updated>
</entry>


</feed>
